Guide to the Undergraduate Affairs, Yale College, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the Dean of Undergraduate Affairs, Yale College, circa 1955-1986; Accession 1991-A-022
  - Records of Undergraduate Student Organizations, 1980-1986
    - On Global Affairs (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Outdoor Corps (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Party of the Right (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Peace Action (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Peace Week Organizing Committee (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Performing Arts Journal (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Pi Beta Phi Fraternity (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Political Roundtable (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Prisoner Film Society (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Proof of the Pudding (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Publius (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Puerto Rican Fine Arts Association (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Queue Magazine (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Redhot and Blue (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Redshift (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Rumor (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Sigma Chi (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Sigma Nu (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Silliman Dramatic Association (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Social Issues Colloquium (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Sociedad Cultural Hispanoamericana (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Society of Orpheus and Bacchus (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Soglasie (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Something Extra (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - South Asian Society (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Spectrum Film Society (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Student Advisory Committee to the AACC (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Student Composers Workshop (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Student Affiliates of the American Chemical Society (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Student Environmental Lobby (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Student Selfcare Exchange (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Students Against Reaganism (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Students for America Alliance (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Students Against Sexual Harassment (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Students for a Negotiated Settlement (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - Students for Nixon (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - Students for a Principled Discussion (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - Students for Mondale (Box 1, Folder 118)
    - Students Valentine Day Service (Box 1, Folder 119)
    - Students with Hart (Box 1, Folder 120)
    - Pan American Society (Box 1, Folder 121)
    - Sub Rosa (Box 1, Folder 122)
    - Tai Chi Ch'uan Society (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Timothy Dwight Dramat (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Tory Party (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Undergraduate Acting Ensemble (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Undergraduate Chess Club (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Undergraduate Concert Committee (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Undergraduate Fund for Families (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Undergraduate Legal Forum (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Undergraduate Literary Forum (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - University Pictures (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Urban Improvement Corps (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Used Book Store (TUBS) (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Walden: Student to Student Counseling (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Whiffenpoofs (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Whim 'n' Rhythm (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Women of Color Alliance (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Women in Science (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Women's Peace Group (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Women's Theater Project (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - The Yale: Student Guide to Yale and New Haven (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Yale Alley Cats (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Yale Amateur Radio Club (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - Yale Banner Publications (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Yale Business and Economic Forum (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - Yale Business Bulletin (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Yale Canadian Student Association (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Yale Collective (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Yale College Bowl Team (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Yale College Class of 1985 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - Yale College Class of 1986 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Yale College Saxophone Quartet (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Yale Discount Book Store (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Yale Experimental Dance Project (Box 2, Folder 155)
    - Yale Film Quarterly (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - Yale Film Society (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - Yale Gay and Lesbian Cooperative (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - Yale Hillel (Box 2, Folder 159)
    - Yale Jewish Appeal (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - Yale Law School Film Society (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - Yale New Haven International Folk Dancers (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - Yale Option (Box 2, Folder 163)
    - Yale Political Monthly (Box 2, Folder 164)
    - Yale Political Roundtable (Box 2, Folder 165)
    - Yale Pundits (Box 2, Folder 166)
    - Yale Record (Box 2, Folder 167)
    - Yale Russian Chorus (Box 2, Folder 168)
    - Yale Scientific Publications (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - Yale Slavic Chorus (Box 2, Folder 170)
    - Yale Spizzwinks (Box 2, Folder 171)
    - Yale Star Trek Society (Box 2, Folder 172)
    - Yale Student Chapter of the Ct. Fund for the Environment (Box 2, Folder 173)
    - Yale Student Commemorative Society (Box 2, Folder 174)
    - Yale Student Committee on Human Sexuality (Box 2, Folder 175)
    - Yale Student Festival Strings (Box 2, Folder 176)
    - Yale Student Shotokan Karate (Box 2, Folder 177)
    - Yale Student Struggle for Soviet Jewry (Box 2, Folder 178)
    - Yale Student Study Group on Int'l Security (Box 2, Folder 179)
    - Yale Student Tech (Box 2, Folder 180)
    - Yale Student Travel Aid (Box 2, Folder 181)
    - Yale Undergraduate Art Review (Box 2, Folder 182)
    - Yale Undergraduate Forum (Box 2, Folder 183)
    - Yeh-lu (Box 2, Folder 184)
    - Zircus- A Yale Literary Journal (Box 2, Folder 185)
    - Yale Student Art History Association (Box 2, Folder 186)
    - Yale Student Art Society (Box 2, Folder 187)
  - Records of Undergraduate Student Organizations and Activities, 1955-1970
    - Senior Proms (Box 3, Folder 188)
    - Prom
      - 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 189)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 190)
      - 1968 (Box 3, Folder 191)
      - Finances (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - Selling and Solicitation
      - 1965 (Box 3, Folder 193)
      - 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - Senior Advisory Board
      - 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 195)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 196 - 197)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 198)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 199)
      - 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 200)
      - 1959-1962 (Box 3, Folder 201)
      - 1957-1961 (Box 3, Folder 202)
    - Senior Class Council (Box 3, Folder 203)
    - Tax Returns Information (Box 3, Folder 204)
    - Undergraduate Activities (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - Senior Societies
      - 1945-1955 (Box 3, Folder 206)
      - 1956-1966 (Box 3, Folder 207)
      - 1967 (Box 3, Folder 208)
      - General and Misc. (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - Ring and Candle (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - St. Elmo's (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - Scroll and Key (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - Skull and Bones (Box 3, Folder 213)
    - Spade and Grave (Box 3, Folder 214)
    - Wolf's Head (Box 3, Folder 215)
    - Parachute Club (Box 3, Folder 216)
    - Party of the Right (Box 3, Folder 217)
    - Phi Beta Sigma (Box 3, Folder 218)
    - Phi Gamma Alpha (Box 3, Folder 219)
    - Phi Gamma Delta (Box 3, Folder 220)
    - PICAL (Box 3, Folder 221)
    - Pi Sigma Alpha (Box 3, Folder 222)
    - Political Union
      - 1958-1962 (Box 3, Folder 223)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 224)
      - 1963 (Box 3, Folder 225)
      - Gardner White Fund (Box 3, Folder 226)
    - Psi Sigma Alpha (Box 3, Folder 227)
    - Psychology Club (Box 3, Folder 228)
    - Pundits (Box 3, Folder 229)
    - Quarterdeck Society (Box 3, Folder 230)
    - Quebec Winter Carnival (Box 3, Folder 231)
    - Radio Club (Box 3, Folder 232)
    - Record, Yale (Publication) (Box 3, Folder 233)
    - Republicans Club (The Young) (Box 3, Folder 234)
    - Renaissance (Box 3, Folder 235)
    - Revolutionary Communist Youth (Box 3, Folder 236)
    - Ripon Society (Box 3, Folder 237)
    - Ruhani Satsang (Box 3, Folder 238)
    - Russian- Club (Box 3, Folder 239)
    - Russian Chorus (Box 3, Folder 240)
    - Seventh Day Adventists (Box 3, Folder 241)
    - St. Thomas More Choir (Box 3, Folder 242)
    - Sigma XI (Honor Scholastic Society) (Box 3, Folder 243)
    - Singing Groups (General information) (Box 3, Folder 244)
    - Sisyphus (Box 3, Folder 245)
    - Student Rescue Committee (Box 3, Folder 246)
    - Yale Scientific (Box 3, Folder 247)
    - Yale Ski Team (Box 3, Folder 248)
    - Yale Speleological Society (Box 3, Folder 249)
    - Yale Slavic Chorus (Box 3, Folder 250)
    - Spizzwinks (Box 3, Folder 251)
    - Y. Socialist Union (Box 3, Folder 252)
    - Southern African Task Force at Yale (Box 3, Folder 253)
    - Sri Chimnoy Meditation Group (Box 3, Folder 254)
    - Yale Standard (Box 4, Folder 255)
    - Student to Student Counseling (Box 4, Folder 256)
    - Students for the Human Services (Box 4, Folder 257)
    - Student Mobilization Committee (Box 4, Folder 258)
    - SDS - RYM (Box 4, Folder 259)
    - Student Volunteer Social Work (Box 4, Folder 260)
    - Students for McGovern (Box 4, Folder 261)
    - Students for N.H. Halfway House (Box 4, Folder 262)
    - Students for Soviet Jewry (Box 4, Folder 263)
    - Students for Yale (Box 4, Folder 264)
    - Sweet Rain (Box 4, Folder 265)
    - Tau Beta Pi (Box 4, Folder 266)
    - Yale Symphonic Society (Box 4, Folder 267)
    - Tennis (Varsity) (Box 4, Folder 268)
    - Third World Coalition (Box 4, Folder 269)
    - Torch Honor Society (Box 4, Folder 270)
    - Torch and Talon (Box 4, Folder 271)
    - Ultramontane Society (Box 4, Folder 272)
    - Ukranian Club at Yale (Box 4, Folder 273)
    - Undergraduate Schools Committee (Box 4, Folder 274)
    - United Nations Association (Box 4, Folder 275 - 276)
    - Urban Improvement Group (Box 4, Folder 277)
    - U.S. Grant (Box 4, Folder 278)
    - Visa (Box 4, Folder 279)
    - Westminster Foundation (Box 4, Folder 280)
    - World Federalists (Box 4, Folder 281)
    - Y.C. Publishing Empire (Box 4, Folder 282)
    - Yale Jazz Ensemble (Box 4, Folder 283)
    - Yale Philippine Association (Box 4, Folder 284)
    - Yale Rifle Club (Box 4, Folder 285)
    - Yale Shih Jung T'ai Chi Chuan Group (Box 4, Folder 286)
    - Yale Symphony Orchestra (Box 4, Folder 287)
    - Yale Undergraduate Physics Society (Box 4, Folder 288)
    - Yale Undergraduate Quarterly (Box 4, Folder 289)
    - Yale U. Provistonal Monarchist Drinking and Debating Society (Box 4, Folder 290)
    - Yavneh, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 291)
    - Young Americans for Freedom (Box 4, Folder 292)
    - Young Israel House at Yale (Box 4, Folder 293)
    - Young People's Socialist League (Box 4, Folder 294)
    - Zero Population Growth (Box 4, Folder 295)
    - Provo (Box 4, Folder 296)
    - P - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 297)
- Records of the Dean of Undergraduate Affairs, Yale College, circa 1955-1986; Accession 1994-A-052
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2027
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Affairs, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Associated Student Agencies, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Affairs Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Materials for Committee on Undergrad. Org., 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Casa Boricua, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Charities Drive (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dramat (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Varsity Fencing Team, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Fence Club (Fraternity) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Black Student Alliance, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Debating Association
    - 1955-1961 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1962- (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Elihu (Senior Society), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Fraternities (IFC), 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Fraternities
    - 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1963- (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Class Council (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha (Zeta Chapter) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Book and Snake (Senior Society) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dwight Hall (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Glee Club, 1956-1961 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Hillel Foundation (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Korean Student Association, 1965- (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Kosher Kitchen (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Manuscript (Senior Society) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Report on Review of Status of Minority Students in YC, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Minority Affairs (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Afro-American Cultural Center
    - Board of Directors, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Minority Student Information (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Minority Class of 1978 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Minority Student Follow-Up (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1976 -- Minority Students (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1977 -- Minority Students (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Yale Black Grad and Professional Student Organization (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Asian American Students (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Puerto Rican Students (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Black Students (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Chicano Students (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Old Campus Problems (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Residential College Room Draws (Steve Corse) (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Housing Allocations, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Annex Housing, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Report on Undergraduate Housing -- YC, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Old Campus Renovation, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Mailing #1 -- Class of '76, 1972 May (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Class of 1977 -- Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Allocation -- Freshman, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Class of 1977 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Freshman Counselor's Mid-Year Reports, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - College Requests -- Class of 1978 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence -- Class of 1978 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Class of 1978 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Class of 1978 and Counselors (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Freshman Mailing -- Class of 1978 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Class of 1978 (Housing Info.) (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Housing, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Faculty Talks -- Class of 1977 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Faculty Talks -- Class of 1978 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Faculty Advisors -- Class of 1977 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Profile of the Class of 1979 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Yale College Council Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Profile -- Class of 1978 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence -- Class of 1979 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - College Requests -- Class of 1979 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Freshman Faculty Advisors -- Class of 1979 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Faculty Advisor -- M. Hill Class of 1979 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Class of 1980 -- Housing (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - PROP
    - Finances, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Final Reports, 1972-1981 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - 1978 (Box 3, Folder 72 - 73)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - 1979 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - 1980 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Operations -- Planning and Administration, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Reading Skills Program, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Academic, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Operations -- Social and Cultural Planning, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Participants, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Operations -- Reading and Study Skills Program, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Follow-Up, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - General Planning, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Participants, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Room Assignments, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Social and Cultural Orientation, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Faculty/Administration Staff (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Invitation Letters (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Follow-Up, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Schedules (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Correspondence (Miscellaneous) (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Operations -- Budgetary Matters, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Financial/Budgetary, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 101 - 102)
    - Housing, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Participants, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Housing, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Academic, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Follow-Up, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Housing for PROP Students, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - General Planning, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Expenses, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - Coordinating Activities (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - General Planning, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Reading Assignments, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Expenses, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Student Enrollment List, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - General Planning, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Yale Summer Orientation Program (Proposal) (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Reading Assignments, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Publicity, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Expenses, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 123)
- Records of the Dean of Student Affairs, Yale College, 1961-2011; 2000-2011; Accession 2016-A-079
  Restricted until January 1, 2047
  - Student Organizations, 1961-2007 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Secret Societies, 1984-2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - General Council, 1988-2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alcohol Policies, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Student Affairs Afro-American Cultural Center, 1990-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alcohol, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Native Americans, 1994-2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fraternities, 1994-2007 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Orientation Class of '99, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Future Freshman, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Latino Cultural Center, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dean Searches, 1997-2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Risk Management, 1997-2007 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Undergraduate Organizations Funding Committee, 1997-2007 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Freshman Orientation Faculty Advisors, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Health Services, 1998-2006 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Student Affairs Afro-American Fundraising, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Police, 1999-2004 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Residential Colleges, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - DANCE, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Information Technology Services (ITS), 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - International Students, 2001-2005 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Security, 2001-2005 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Racial/Ethnic, 2003-2006 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Organizations, 2003-2006 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Minority Advisory Council (MAC), 2003-2007 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Singing Groups, 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Freshman, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Race Specific Programs, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Peer Institutions, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Freshman, 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Native American Conference, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Hurricane Emergency Relief Organization, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - LGBT, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Nakanishi Prize, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Women's Center, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - ACE Fellows, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Occupational Hazard and Safety Act (OSHA), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Publications Council, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Realizing Race, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Symphony, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Committee on Diversity, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Yale College, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Studies, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - The Yale-Harvard Game, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - The Yale-Harvard Game, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Residential College Counselors, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Ethnic Counselors, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Freshman Reallocation Class of '90 and '91, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Freshman Counselors, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Freshman Counselors Class of '96, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Ethnic Counselors Class of '97, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Counselors Class of '97, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Ethnic Counselors Class of '99, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Frocos Program, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Freshman Counselors Class of '99, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Head Counselors, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Freshman Class of '00, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Freshman Counselors (Frocos), 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Ethnic Counselors Class of '00, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Residential College Counselors Class of '00, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Skindeep, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Class of 2001, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Counselors Class of '01, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Frocos, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Froco Handbook, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Counselor Orientation Class of 01, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Pre-orientation programs Class of '01, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Pre-registration program Class of '02, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Class of 2002, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Freshman Counselors Class of '02, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Froco Handbook, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Frocos, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Pre-orientation Class of '03, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Freshman Class of 2003, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Handicapped Students Class of '03, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Freshman Counselors Class of '03, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Freshman Counselor Orientation Class of '03, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Freshman Orientation Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Freshman Class of '04, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Freshman Counselor Orientation Class of '04, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Freshman Counselors Class of '05, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Counselors Class of '05, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Freshman Counselor Orientation Class of '06, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Ethnic Counselor Programming/Restructure, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Ethnic Counselors, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Freshman Counselor Orientation Class of '07, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Freshman Counselor Orientation Class of '08, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Ethnic Counselor Assignments, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Woon Report, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Advising Ethnic Counselors, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - July Mailing Class of '00, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Counselors Class of '06, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Freshman Orientation Class of '09, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Head Counselors, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Freshman Faculty Advisors, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Ethnic Counselor Program, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Sexual Harrassment Grievance Board (SHGB), 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Essay Contest, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Freshman Orientation Essay, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - July Mailing Class of '12, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Calendar of Days Class of '12, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Faculty Advisors, 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Freshman Handbook Class of '12, 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Pre-orientation, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Orientation Class of '12, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - May Mailing Class of '12, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - May Mailing Class of '12, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - July Mailing List Class of '12, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Froco Mailing Class of '13, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Handbook, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Freshman Counselor Handbook, 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Freshman Orientation Class of '13, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - July Mailing Calendar of Opening Days (COD) Class of '13, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - July Mailing Class of '13, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Son Daughter July Mailing Class of '13, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Alcohol Mailing December, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - May Mailing Class of '14, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Alcohol Mailing Class of '14, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Alcohol Handbook Class of '14, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Orientation Class of '14, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 1)